[
    {
    "id": "01",
    "question": "On a wet road how do you make an emergency stop?",
    "answer": {
    "a": "Using front and rear brakes.",
    "b": "Using front brake only.",
    "c": "Using rear brake only.",
    "d": "Using the clutch."
    },
    "correct": "a"
    },
    {
    "id": "02",
    "question": "You should use your right-hand indicator when -",
    "answer": {
    "a": "You intend to move to the right.",
    "b": "You intend to slow down.",
    "c": "You are about to stop.",
    "d": "You intend to move to the left."
    },
    "correct": "a"
    },
    {
    "id": "03",
    "question": "If you have a crash whilst wearing your helmet you should -",
    "answer": {
    "a": "Check that it's not damaged.",
    "b": "Get it repainted.",
    "c": "Replace it.",
    "d": "Sell it."
    },
    "correct": "c"
    },
    {
    "id": "04",
    "question": "In what part of the lane should you ride when being passed by on-coming vehicles?",
    "answer": {
    "a": "No special part of your lane.",
    "b": "As close to the centre line.",
    "c": "The centre or left of your lane.",
    "v5": "As close to the sidewalk."
    },
    "correct": "c"
    },
    {
    "id": "05",
    "question": "Wearing a helmet visor or goggles when riding will -",
    "answer": {
    "a": "Protect your eyes.",
    "b": "Make you look awkward.",
    "c": "Not make much difference.",
    "d": "B and C"
    },
    "correct": "a"
    },
    {
    "id": "06",
    "question": "At low speeds, if the front tyre goes flat what is the first thing you will notice?",
    "answer": {
    "a": "The steering will feel heavy.",
    "b": "The motorcycle will tend to slide",
    "c": "The motorcycle will lean heavily",
    "d": "The motorcycle will gain speed"
    },
    "correct": "a"
    },
    {
    "id": "07",
    "question": "In a turn you should tell a pillion passenger to -",
    "answer": {
    "a": "Lean against you",
    "b": "Lean with you.",
    "c": "Stay upright.",
    "d": "Lean to the back."
    },
    "correct": "b"
    },
    {
    "id": "08",
    "question": "If you wear regular spectacles while you ride -",
    "answer": {
    "a": "You should also wear a visor.",
    "b": "You must not ride at night.",
    "c": "You need no eye protection.",
    "d": "You can not ride a motorrcycle."
    },
    "correct": "a"
    },
    {
    "id": "09",
    "question": "If you find cracks or loose padding in your helmet you should -",
    "answer": {
    "a": "Use duct tape to fix it.",
    "b": "Have it repaired.",
    "c": "sell it it.",
    "d": "Replace it."
    },
    "correct": "d"
    },
    {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "When stopping at trafic lights, you should put which foot on the ground?",
    "answer": {
    "a": "right foot",
    "b": "Left foot",
    "c": "Both of them",
    "d": "Does not matter"
    },
    "correct": "b"
    },
    {
    "id": "11",
    "question": "What is the right lever on the handle bar used for?",
    "answer": {
    "a": "Apply the rear brake.",
    "b": "Apply the front clutch.",
    "c": "Apply the front brake.",
    "d": "Change the speed."
    },
    "correct": "c"
    },
    {
    "id": "12",
    "question": "The right foot pedal is for -",
    "answer": {
    "a": "Applying the rear brake.",
    "b": "Signaling right.",
    "c": "Increasing the speed.",
    "d": "Applying the clutch"
    },
    "correct": "a"
    },
    {
    "id": "13",
    "question": "You should use the left foot pedal for -",
    "answer": {
    "a": "Applying the rear brake.",
    "b": "Open the throttle.",
    "c": "Change the gear.",
    "d": "Applying the front brake."
    },
    "correct": "c"
    },
    {
    "id": "14",
    "question": "Counter steering while turning right, you -",
    "answer": {
    "a": "Turn the handle bar right.",
    "b": "Turn the handle bar left.",
    "c": "Use the throttle to turn.",
    "d": "Do nothing."
    },
    "correct": "b"
    },
    {
    "id": "15",
    "question": "You bought new tyres. The first ride, you should - ",
    "answer": {
    "a": "Try to reach max speed. ",
    "b": "Break the tyres in.",
    "c": "Try drifting.",
    "d": "Ride like always."
    },
    "correct": "b"
    }
    ]